+919999748948



ketandutt.github.io



ketan.dutt@yahoo.in



Dwarka, New Delhi, 110059



KETAN DUTT

Senior Game Developer

EDUCATION

B.Tech in IT Kurukshetra University | 2013 - 2017

12th CBSE

Mira Model Sr. Sec. School | 2013

10th CBSE

Mira Model Sr. Sec. School | 2011

LANGUAGES



JavaScript

C

Java

HTML/CSS

Python

SKILLS

Creativity

A passion for video games Wide knowledge of gaming trends Strong analytical frame of mind Ability to work as part of a team

ABOUT ME

I am a highly adaptable professional with over 5 years of work experience and a track record of success in leadership, problemsolving, and workflow management. I am seeking to use my abilities to excel in the role of Game Developer at your company.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Game Developer at Extramarks

November 2021 - May 2022

- Received "Rookie Rockstar Award" in first 2 months.
- Designed a system using the Phaser Game Framework that enabled rapid prototyping and testing for game creation. This system has been utilized by my coworkers to develop over 15 games and is still in use today. I personally completed 6 games using this system.
- Maintained and modified existing Unity projects to fix errors and adapt to new requirements.

Game Developer Rendered Ideas Softgame Pvt. Ltd.

June 2018 - November 2021

- Worked on more than 20 games with backend and server-side Development.
- Developed 2D and 3D Games using LibGDX, Unity, and Godot Game Engine.
- Published many games on Google Play Store, Amazon App Store,
 Roku Channel Store, and many HTML-based platforms.
- Experience with the game's Backend, Server-Side, Ad/IAP Management, cross-promotion, etc.
- Created many Web Development-based projects using JavaScript, PHP, and MySQL.

Traniee Developer at Akashvaani.com

May 2017 - June 2018

 Updating and improving an existing website to resolve issues and meet new needs.